Lloyd: So now that you've completed
session three of unit three, it's
time to complete the relevant
section in the assessment booklet.
So if you open your assessment booklet
and scroll down to section three,
you will see that this is about
ethical conduct in cyber security.
And the learning objectives at the
top, where it is in the assessment
and where the information can be
found in the course materials.
There are only two
questions in this section.
The first one is asking you to describe
ethical conduct within cyber security.
So what behavior is ethical?
What is it that people in cyber
security do that is ethical?
And then the alternative to that in
box two, it's asking you to describe
unethical conduct so that's the opposite.
So what is unethical conduct
within cyber security?
Once you've done that you can then
check through the whole assessment,
do a spelling and grammar check.
Make sure you're happy with all of your
responses and save the assessment and
send it through to your tutor for marking.